screencloud.net 2013-11-26

# ScreenCloud | Privacy Policy

###### Version 01

* * *

###### This document

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by screencloud.net and how it is used. It also covers subdomains of screencloud.net like blog.screencloud.net and others.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [contact@screencloud.net](mailto:contact@screencloud.net). 

###### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, screencloud.net makes use of **log files**. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

###### Cookies and Web Beacons

screencloud.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Cookies are also used to **track if a user is logged in** and allow access to certain pages if they are.

###### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a **third party** vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on screencloud.net.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to screencloud.net and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:   

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on the website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

We have **no access to or control over** these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to **opt-out** of certain practices. screencloud.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. Please note that you will be **unable to login** to screencloud.net with cookies disabled.

###### Security of your information

We take steps and precautions to secure your data on our servers, but we **cannnot guarantee or warrant** the security of any information you provide to us. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.

Please note that all screenshots are public by default. This means that they can be viewed by anyone with the screencloud link (e.g: <http://screencloud.net/v/cVAW>) and be indexed by search engines. It's therefore not recommended to upload screenshots containing any sensitive information.
